[REDACTED -- PERSONNEL]
Yeah.
I can.
Hi.
Do we press L right now or --
[REDACTED -- PERSONNEL]
Do we press L to mark right now?
()
[REDACTED -- PERSONNEL]
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can.
Uh, do you know how to do this?
Oh, maybe you have to go through, (I guess).
Uh.
Okay, wait let me see.
Wait let me see.
Yeah.
Can we go through?
Oh, yeah, I can.
Wait.
(Can) -- can you come here maybe?
Wait, let -- let me go and find you.
Real quick.
(Go).
Well.
Do you know how to (portal)?
Oh wait, let me go to the other side and uh maybe just press on to this like red button right now and let me go to the other side to let you through.
Yeah.
Cool.
()
Yeah.
And go through the other door.
Yeah, cool.
And is there anything I can do right now?
Wait.
How?
Huh.
Don't actually know how it works.
Right.
Huh.
Wait.
Well.
Mhm.
Ah, yeah.
I see, I see.
I see.
There's also an orange-like camera thing in -- in the room that is like inside.
(That room).
(But) -- but I kinda am, kinda confused.
((sneezes))
Thank you.
Thanks.
Ugh, wow.
Hm.
Ooh.
Ah, you got like squeezed ... to death.
Sorry about that.
Ugh.
Let me try.
How does it work, how does it work?
Okay.
Oh.
Can I please try inside to -- to see?
Like, can you stand on this?
Wait, wait.
Cool.
Uh.
Don't know what it means.
Can you stand on this to let me through for --
Oh, thanks.
And uh, yeah.
And uh --
Can -- can you stand on that one?
Oh, I'm really confused right now.
How does the portal thing work?
I --
There's the primary (portal) --
Oh!
Oh.
Ah.
Oh, look.
If we like --
Wait.
This the ... secondary portal.
Wait, I right-clicked my mouse and this comes the purple thing.
Did -- did you see the purple thing there?
Yeah, I -- I -- I don't know how it works.
I don't know why it works.
It's just --
I got the portal stuff.
And I don't know how ... it's going to help us.
Uh.
Oof.
Oh, I see.
I think we can only open portals in this kind of -- in this kind of materials.
So if I go something like this kind of --
Yeah () see that.
That's cool.
So we can only put our portal on this kind of like porous material.
So if I go --
Ah.
That's cool.
And uh I can go -- I can go to that place.
Yeah, and uh --
Yeah, you stay inside, uh you stay inside and uh--
Oh wait, let -- let -- let me think how -- how we -- we should do this.
Yeah, cool.
So, uh can -- how -- how do I get the portal?
Okay, I see, I see.
So maybe you can go to the other side uh.
And uh stay there.
Go to like the -- the -- the room with the like --
That -- that one.
The room over there.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Definitely.
You can also use the portal.
Ah, oops.
Yeah.
And uh --
Cool.
And --
Oh, I know.
Ah.
Damn.
Uh.
Okay, uh.
I know, I know, I know.
So ... uh here's the thing.
Yeah, and uh also put a portal, like, here, alright?
Put a portal, like, somewhere here.
Like, in -- in my room.
I'll let you through.
Put a portal in my room that connects to your like --
Yeah.
You can just put the --
Yeah, and uh --
Cool.
Yeah, you can get out and uh ... put a portal, say, here.
Put your other (portal) --
Yeah, and uh --
Cool.
And we can get through.
And I think uh --
And uh let’s come -- yeah, we got through.
We got through.
Cool.
So it takes two.
Yeah, and we can proceed to the next level.
I think that means ().
Yeah, cool.
Nice job.
Okay, this is the --
Hm.
Yeah!