[REDACTED -- PERSONNEL]
Okay.
Alright.
I (accidentally filled this out) ().
That's totally fine.
Okay.
Alright, thank you.
[REDACTED -- PERSONNEL]
Thank you.
Hello.
Yeah.
Can you hear me?
Alright.
Mm.
Oh.
I suppose.
I put the () in here.
()
Where are you?
Oh.
Sorry.
Alright then.
Oh, I have an idea.
Maybe.
There's this ... ah orange thing on camera.
Does that have to hit somewhere perhaps?
()
Um.
Bless you.
()
(Let me) come back next to you.
Fuck.
()
Oh.
((laughs))
Ah, it’s okay.
What's this?
Alright.
()
What happened?
Yeah yeah yeah.
Uh.
Try (hitting) -- try hitting the camera with um the purple thing, maybe.
If you direct the camera towards the portal with the purple ... uh gun, it might open up a portal.
Oh.
Ah, oh.
Mm.
Mhm, oh can you hold this door for me?
()
Okay, I put a portal here.
Okay.
How did this open?
Nice.
Yeah.
Ugh.
Well, this is kind of fun.