Mm.
Okay, press L.
()
There, I guess.
Huh.
There's a portal here.
I can place one to see what happens.
And uh ... this one here.
Can see what it does.
Does it do anything?
Oh.
I kinda (honestly) --
Wait, wait.
Did you see anything happen?
The -- the -- something got like --
The hatch get opened over there, but I don't really know what --
Oh, let me see.
Maybe I can --
Oof.
Ah, I see.
Can you please --
()
Uh.
I don’t know, maybe we can ... ask.
I -- I -- I don't know, maybe no, I guess.
Maybe no.
So this --
Yeah.
Uh.
I guess this is for the researchers to like synchronize the -- the recording so, but you can ask them, I guess.
Anyway.
So can (you) -- can you please come here to the red button?
Yeah.
And uh let me go through the portal.
Cool.
And can you please --
Oh wait!
Don't -- don't go through the portal (yet).
Uh, anyway  I --
Yeah.
And uh can you press the uh the red button over there?
I mean (over) -- over there.
Yeah.
I --
(Sorry) -- sorry.
Uh the button uh (over) -- over there at the -- the place we respawned.
Like --
Yeah that -- that one.
Did you see that?
Ooh.
Me, that's me, that's me.
Yeah.
Yeah and uh come close and press E.
Yeah, and I can go through and uh --
Uh.
()
Okay.
Let me see, let me see.
The purple one.
You can go through the portal right now.
The -- the -- the -- my blue portal.
Yeah.
The portal that is behind you.
Yeah, (you’re) -- you're looking at the right direction, and you can come through.
Cool.
And uh --
Yeah, here we go.
Yeah, and uh --
Hm, let me see what this place is for.
Uh, do you think there's a --
I don't know.
What -- what does this mean?
Oh.
Wait, (where) -- where are -- okay, cool.
What's this do?
Agh, let me see.
Hm.
Got confused.
Press, press, press, press.
Press.
Uh, nothing really happened.
Oh, look at -- look up there.
Uh.
Before we press the button --
Um.
All four like --
Oh yeah, did you see the like -- the color changes?
If we press the button, (this uh) color is going to change from -- from uh -- from blue to orange over there
Right.
So maybe we should find the next two one.
The -- the two ones should be somewhere inside so --
Hm.
Uh.
Oh I see we can place a portal up there.
And you can place a portal there.
Uh you -- you place -- I place a portal there so --
(Sorry), did you see my portal?
Up -- up here.
You can place it to the like -- there.
On the left side.
Yeah, and uh we can place another portal to get inside.
Have to do it quick though though.
We have to synchronize our moves.
There’s -- there ain't much time for us to like uh --
Yeah, and I've got to --
Uh and press that one.
And uh press this one.
Uh (something) -- something's failing.
Oof.
Let's synchronize our move.
Let's get to a closest button.
We press the first button.
Like, on my mark, we press the button, we get into the portal, we press another button, and we rush to the (finish) -- rush to the door.
The hatch over there, right?
Cool.
Did you like --
Three, two, one, on my mark, go.
(Let's) -- let's do this.
Here, let's press one button and press the other one, and try to ... press the third, maybe.
And uh --
Oof.
Yeah, and uh now we can stand here, I guess.
Something's out.
Did you see that?
Yeah.
So, what is this?
Oh, we might have to put the ball on it, I guess.
We can like (drop) --
Yeah.
Damn, this game is -- I don't know.
Can I interact?
Oh, I can use interact!
If I press E, I can, like, put this up and uh drop this to the ... desired location.
And uh here we go.
That's cool.
((hums))
Yeah, nice.